ontheroad.to 2013-05-22

# OnTheRoad | Privacy

**Commitment to Your Privacy**

This site is owned and operated by Devmasters Corporation (Devmasters). We understand you value your privacy. At Devmasters, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. This statement governs information you provide to us or we learn from your use of this web site and tells you how we may collect, use, and in some instances share this information.

**Information Devmasters Collects**

Devmasters gathers two types of information about this websites users:

  * Personal information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions, such as email and online registration forms to Devmasters. Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, your name, home address, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card information such as the credit card number, card verification value, and the billing address. The types and amount of personal information collected for these activities will vary depending on the activity or service for which you have registered or accessed the website. 
  * Devmasters also gathers non-personal information through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This non-personal information collected includes click-throughs, IP addresses, and usage data. This non-personal information allows us to better tailor our content to site users needs.

Devmasters gathers user information as follows:

**How Devmasters Collects and Uses Personal Information**

We ask the user for personal information when they register. Devmasters collects personal information to provide the registered users with Devmasters content through email and other content made available through the Service. The personal information collected includes the users name and email. Birth date information may be verified but is not retained. If you prefer to not receive additional emails you are given the opportunity to opt-out of future emails when you receive your first email. Additionally, you may contact us through the webform available at: www.ontheroad.to/about

Personal information is also collected through billing forms used in relation to any payments you are required to make for the Service. The personal information collected for billing includes the users name, physical address, and credit card information. Devmasters limits the use of information collected for billing purposes to the purpose for which it is shared by you with us.

Finally, the user may decide to enter additional personal information by adding it to their Devmasters service profile. The user may allow this personal information to be viewed by other users of the Devmasters service. 

  * **Usage tracking -** We track product usage data to improve the services we offer to our users. We collect user traffic patterns throughout our site. This information is collected to help improve site flow and usability. In addition, we track click-through information, including IP addresses, to our site from the reports and emails we sent to our customers. This is done to gauge the effectiveness of our communications with customers and to discourage fraudulent use. However, we do not correlate this information with the personal information of individual users. 
  * **Cookies -** We may place a text file called a cookie in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain personal information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Devmasters may use cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). In addition, Devmasters uses encrypted cookies to authenticate the user on each page after the user logs onto the website. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. If you turn cookies off, you will not be able to log in to your account on the Web and will not be able to access some portions of the Devmasters website. 
  * **Children -** Consistent with laws we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requiring parental consent. Any person who provides their personal information to Devmasters through this web site represents that they are 13 years of age or older. 
  * **User Access -** You have access to and the ability to edit all of your personal information by logging in and then going to the Preferences section of the Devmasters website. 

**Devmasters Transfer and Information Sharing Policy**

We provide information we receive from you to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf for performing the Service and other purposes identified above. We do not share personal information collected on this web site with third parties for their direct marketing purposes without your consent. Devmasters does not share personal information about site users with third parties unless doing so is appropriate to carry out a users request or it reasonably believes that doing so is legally required or is in Devmasterss interest to protect its property or other legal rights or the rights or property of others. Devmasters shares non-personal information in anonymous aggregate form with third parties. This non-personal information is used by third parties to help Devmasters improve the Website and Devmasters service.

  * **Merger or Bankruptcy -** If Devmasters should ever file for bankruptcy or have its assets sold to or merge with another entity, information Devmasters receives from you from this Site is a Devmasters asset and may be transferred.

**International Visitors and Customers**

This web site is hosted in the United States and is intended for United States visitors. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and by providing your personal data you consent to:

  * the use of your personal data for the purposes identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and 
  * the transfer of your personal data to the United States as indicated above.

**Safe Harbor Certification**

Devmasters adheres to the Safe Harbor principles negotiated between the United States and the EU regarding data protection for customer data and personal data Devmasters receives when you register for its services or use its web site. Accordingly, when visiting this web site or providing personal data to Devmasters, Devmasters has taken steps to ensure the adequate protection of the processing of your personal data. 

**Security**

While Devmasters does take steps to ensure that your personal data is protected against unauthorized or unlawful use and accidental loss or damage, no data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. We use secure server software (SSL) and firewalls to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software.

If Devmasters learns of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using this web site or providing personal information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of this site. Devmasters may post a notice on our web site if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to view the Devmasters.com web site. Devmasters may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us at [privacy@Ontheroad.to](mailto:privacy@Ontheroad.to).

**Changes and Updates**

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the last updated date on the Privacy Policy. For changes to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing the change. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the Personal Information we collect. Your continued use of this web site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Statement and any updates.

**Contacting Devmasters**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [privacy@Ontheroad.to](mailto:privacy@Ontheroad.to)

If you have a privacy concern regarding Devmasters or this policy and if you cannot satisfactorily resolve it through the use of this web site you should then write to: [privacy@Ontheroad.to](mailto:privacy@Ontheroad.to). In the event that we are still unable to resolve your concerns Devmasters is committed to cooperating to achieve a proper resolution of your privacy concerns.
